<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Gndec Notes</title>
    <link>https://gndecnotes.com/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Gndec Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://gndecnotes.com/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Careers vs jobs</title>
      <link>https://gndecnotes.com/blogs/careers-vs-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gndecnotes.com/blogs/careers-vs-jobs/</guid>
      <description>What does it mean to have a career? Having a career could mean that the person is changing jobs over and over again, or they might want to be like a company or employer and work in a certain role for years or maybe even a career. An example of this is a sales executive. People become leaders in companies, if they work hard they can become a director in a company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future of Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://gndecnotes.com/blogs/future-of-cryptocurrency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gndecnotes.com/blogs/future-of-cryptocurrency/</guid>
      <description>What is Cryptocurrency? In short, cryptocurrency is a kind of digital currency. It’s also referred to as virtual currency because there is no physical coin or coin in this case. Cryptocurrency is decentralized digital cash without a central bank. It’s been designed by the developers and they keep the transactions encrypted. This prevents someone from hacking the system and sending double payments or stealing the money. The system also prevents the system from being exploited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What AI Means for Us: The Future of Technology and Humanity</title>
      <link>https://gndecnotes.com/blogs/what-ai-means-for-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gndecnotes.com/blogs/what-ai-means-for-us/</guid>
      <description>What is AI? If you had asked me a few years ago what AI was, I would have answered that it&amp;rsquo;s software that tells computers to do certain things. In the past, AI has been mostly done with the objective of computer systems performing specific tasks faster and better than humans. The first automated financial trading system was developed around 1990 and later real time trading on the stock market came into being in 1997.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the Future of Electric Cars Looks Bright</title>
      <link>https://gndecnotes.com/blogs/future-of-electric-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gndecnotes.com/blogs/future-of-electric-cars/</guid>
      <description>What are Electric Cars? They are a car that does not use petrol as a fuel and instead relies on electricity. This can be generated from a variety of different sources, such as solar panels, wind farms or other sources of energy that we produce on site. Electric cars offer the advantage of the same level of efficiency and fuel efficiency as petrol or diesel cars. The only difference is the fact that there is no petrol or diesel involved.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
